Vasile Cudalb

Moldova

cudalb.vasile@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/vasile-cudalb-98441497

Summary

I am an experienced Senior .NET Developer with more than eight years of expertise in the field of software development.

Throughout my career, I have held roles as both a team leader and a team member, which has provided me with a strong ability to work effectively within a team setting. I am always eager to take on intricate challenges and embrace risks without hesitation.

My dedication to enhancing the development process drives me to continuously explore new techniques, approaches, and technologies. By doing so, I strive to create faster, more reliable, reusable, practical, and userfriendly solutions for clients.

My technical proficiency includes:

Main stack: C#, .NET Core/Framework, MS SQL/MongoDB, Redis, REST APIs, gRCP, Message Brokers(RabbitMq, Azure Service Bus), JavaScript and Angular.

Testing: NUnit, Xunit, SpecFlow, Selenium, k6.

CI/CD: Docker, Docker Compose, Github Actions.

Experience



案 Senior .NET Developer

Seavus

Apr 2023 - Present (10 months)

Solution Lead

Software Mind Romania & Moldova

Oct 2022 - Mar 2023 (6 months)

Fintech solution that provides on-demand access to SME financial information.

- Being in charge of technical solution design process and validation.
- Monitoring and planning the development of technical aspects/debts.
- Improving branching and release strategy workflow.
- Validating user stories readiness from a development perspective.
- Creating architectural diagrams and documentation.

🚫 Senior .NET Developer

Software Mind Romania & Moldova

Jul 2021 - Oct 2022 (1 year 4 months)

Betting platform that incorporates both a sportsbook and a back-office management tool.

- Designing and developing high-performance and scalable betting application.
- Analyzing clients needs and software requirements to determine the design feasibility within time and performance constraints.
- Coming up with architecture solutions for BE team (including diagrams/flow charts, communication between micro-services, SDK structure, etc).
- Implementation of specifications based on the received tasks including analyzing and bug fixing.
- Developing lambda functions used to handle betting events.
- Interacting with AWS S3 to store system content and reports.
- Writing documentation on the existing and new functionalities in a structured and consistent way.
- Implementing new micro-services and setting up the communication between them.
- Covering the source code with unit tests.
- Leading the development team for 8 months.
- Setting up Azure Pipelines for builds and deploy.
- Mentoring internship.

Senior .NET Developer

Stefanini EMEA

Jan 2021 - Jun 2021 (6 months)

Fund and investing portal.

- Upgrading/migrating the system from .NET Core 2.0 to .NET Core 3.1.
- Extending the platform with new functionalities based on the PO's requirements.
- Covering modules with unit and integration tests.
- Managing secrets and keys by using AWS key vault.
- Performing crud operations on AWS MongoDb.
- Adding cron jobs and windows services.
- Modifying and fixing DevExpress views.

Senior .NET Developer

Stefanini EMEA

Sep 2019 - Dec 2020 (1 year 4 months)

Retailer and logistics software provider that enables smooth logistics, transactions, operations, and customer journeys.

- Developing scalable and high-performance REST APIs.
- Adding new features and modules based on the client desires covering with unit and SpecFlow tests.
- Extending UI with new components using AngularJS.
- Interacting directly with clients during the technical debt and platform analyzing meetings.
- Refactoring and increasing performance of the less effective modules of the application.
- Setting up GitHub Actions for builds, package publishing and deploys.
- Mentoring internship.

.NET Developer

Stefanini EMEA

Oct 2017 - Aug 2019 (1 year 11 months)

Fintech provider of the expert shareholder, pension, remediation and credit services.

- Developing new micro-services including REST APIs and the entire communication.
- Adjusting existing app layers/modules and functionality.
- Adding new features and modules.
- Covering the newly added modules with units and acceptances tests using NUnit and SpecFlow;
- Induction and hand over for new joiners.
- Optimization DB queries using profiler.
- Creating MS Server procedures and functions.
- Implementing Auth microservice from scratch using Identity Server.

AM .NET Engineer

Endava

Nov 2016 - Oct 2017 (1 year)

Banking and reporting service provider.

- Developing new application modules and services.
- Storing, retrieving and manipulating data for future analysis of the system capabilities.
- Optimizing database's queries and procedures.
- Adding new UI features and functionality using WebForms.
- Resolving incidents and implementing change requests raised by customers.
- Validation the workflow to ensure that the desired results are produced.

*.... AM .NET Engineer

Endava

Jun 2015 - Oct 2016 (1 year 5 months)

Customer satisfaction measurement dashboard/platform.

- Modifying existing software to solve the errors, adjusting it to the new hardware and improving its performance.
- Adding new endpoints/functionality (mainly MVC controllers and UI charts).
- Implementing cron jobs in order to sync data with a third party system.
- Improving application reliability and readability.
- 6 months leading a team of 4 members during the active development stage.
- Coaching new members during the development period.
- Resolving Incidents, implementing Change Requests

• Internship Program

Endava

Mar 2015 - Jun 2015 (4 months)

Developing a social network messaging platform based on the obtained knowledge during the internship program.

Education

Academy of Economic Studies of Moldova

Licentiate Engineer, Information Technologies 2015 - 2020

Financial Banking College "A.Diordita"

Bachelors, Automation Engineer Technology/Technician 2011 - 2015

Skills

.NET Core • C# • Entity Framework • Docker Products • Git • MongoDB • Redis • Solution Architecture